tapinfluence.com 2016-04-20

# TapInfluence Privacy Policy

**TapInfluence  
****Privacy Policy**

** ** This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which TapInfluence collects, uses, and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User“) of the [http://www.tapinfluence.com](http://www.tapinfluence.com/) website (“Site“). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by TapInfluence.

**_Personal information_**

Personal information refers to information that is connected to a User’s name, and may include things such as a User’s email address, mailing address, telephone number, and demographic information. TapInfluence collects personal information when Users voluntarily submit it to us. For example, we may collect personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources that we make available on our Site.

In addition to personal information that we may receive from Users, TapInfluence may collect other information from Users using the following technologies:

  * _Cookies_. “Cookies” are small bits of information that the Site places on the hard drive of a User’s computer. Cookies remember information about activities on the Site to make a User’s visits to the Site more enjoyable and valuable by providing a customized experience and recognizing a User’s preferences. If a User has chosen to disable cookies on his or her browser, some of the functionality of the Site may be lost. Certain services provided by TapInfluence, require that cookies be enabled in a User’s browser and cannot be used when cookies are disabled.
  * _Flash Cookies_. (also called Local Shared Objects or “LSOs”). Flash cookies are data files similar to cookies, except that they can store more complex data. Flash cookies are used to remember settings, preferences, and usage, particularly for video, interactive gaming, and other similar services.
  * _Web beacons or clear pixels_. Web beacons are small graphic images on a web page or in an email that can be used for such things as recording the pages and advertisements that a User selects, or tracking the performance of email marketing campaigns.
  * _Web server logs_. Web server logs are records of activity created by the computer that delivers the webpages requested by the User’s browser. For example, a web server log may record the search term entered or the link clicked to bring a User a webpage. The web server log also may record information about a User’s browser, such as IP address and the cookies set on the browser by the server.
  * _Device information_. We may collect information about the mobile device or computer used to access the Site, including without limitation the hardware model, operating system and version, browser type, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information.

TapInfluence participates in behavioral-based advertising. This means that a third party may use technology (e.g., a cookie) to collect information about a User’s use of the Site so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to a User’s interest. That advertising may appear either on the Site, or on other websites.

**_How we use personal information_**

TapInfluence may use a User’s personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve customer service_. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _To personalize user experience_. We may use personal information to understand how our Users use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _To improve our Site_. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_. To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _To send periodic emails_. We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User joins our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**_How we protect personal information_**

We use reasonable measures to help prevent personal information from becoming disclosed to individuals who are not described in this policy. While TapInfluence attempts to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and TapInfluence cannot promise that information about you will remain secure in all circumstances.

**_Sharing your personal information_**

TapInfluence may share a User’s personal information with companies that are affiliated with us (that is, that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with TapInfluence). TapInfluence may also share a User’s personal information with third parties who advertise their products and services on the Site or other third parties who would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, TapInfluence may offer a discount or contest in conjunction with a co-sponsor that may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to a User. In such a case, a User’s personal information may be shared with the co-sponsor and their use of such User’s personal information is governed by their privacy policy.

There may be instances when TapInfluence may disclose personal information without providing a User with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of TapInfluence, other affiliated companies or their employees, agents, and contractors; to protect the safety and security of other Users; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if TapInfluence sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, TapInfluence may transfer personal information to a third party as part of that transaction.

**_Third party websites_**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**_Changes to this privacy policy_**

TapInfluence has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**_California residents_**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents who have an established business relationship with Syttr are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. This notice will identify the categories of information shared with and will include a list of the third parties with which it is shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to us at the addresses listed below.

**_Contacting us_**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:

TapInfluence  
2100 Central Ave, STE 200  
Boulder, CO  
720-726-4074  

If TapInfluence needs, or is required, to contact you concerning any event that involves information about you we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.

_This document was last updated on December 4, 2015_
